[{"answer": "Naughty out of hurdle, maybe, yes.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "You're quite a naughty girl, aren't you, Vanessa?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "If I were you, I'd be doing what you know is right and nothing less in that process.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What should I do?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Completely extraordinary.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "This is an extraordinary development after so long, isn't it?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Scandalous, yes.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "I mean this could have been pretty scandalous, isn't it, that this man, if he is the guy that did this, has been allowed to roam the streets for 33 years?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Well, we feel that some crimes are nonbondable offense and second-degree murder is one of these, Piers.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "How does the family feel about the potential for George Zimmerman being released on bail tomorrow?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, let me first say that Sybrina Fulton is a Christian woman.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Tell me why, and also tell me is it a possibility this meeting could happen in the future do you think?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, obviously it's going to be very emotional being in the same room with the killer of your child.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "How are they feeling about that?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "In some ways, this is the perfect judge, if you're a defense lawyer, to have make this decision.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What do you think that means for the possibility of George Zimmerman being released on bail?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "I -- all things considered, I think it is likely.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Is it likely, do you think, all things considered he'll be released?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "It's -- I've never seen a published case that argues that.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Well, I'm just asking, I mean, does that come into play as a factor in such a high-profile case, that not that he's a threat to other people but that his own life might be actually at risk and he's better off actually being inside, not on bail?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "In their effort to keep him inside, can we expect new evidence to emerge by the prosecution tomorrow?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "It's a great question, because I think, no.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Is it more difficult to get a conviction under the second-degree murder charge he's on?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "It really is.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "It's a fascinating case, isn't it?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, they all have something different.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "What do they need from somebody like you?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "It's not a say, it's putting him back in state.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "When that specific thing is happening, what do you say?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, you know, if you're thinking about yourself in a moment like that, you can't really serve, so then it would be all about you.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "I mean despite all these incredible things that you've experienced, to have the president of your country call you in his great hour of need?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Self-doubt as often as you do.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Do you personally ever have crushing moments of self- doubt?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "That was pretty horrific.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Now be honest, when you first heard that, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Well, clearly it's not just about inner self-belief, it's really about people getting to the truth.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "How helpful is that to exuding the kinds of inner self-belief that you clearly have?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Did she ever tell you she loved you?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Sounds like perfect.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I'm a strategist.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What does he need?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "In one minute or two?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "It's the health side.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "What's the last one of your five points?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, there was a large part that was fantastic and positive and overwhelming.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "What are you thinking when it all started erupting like this?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Yeah, partly.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Do you feel that you achieved that goal?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Do you think you would have had the platform to realize your dreams?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "You have no idea.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "You weren't quite what your teachers thought, were you?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "I loved Whilemina.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "That was a great part, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Wearing fabulous clothing and bossing people around.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Stuff you dream of, isn't it?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "So I know that that, in the end, is the glue, isn't it?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Oh, boy.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "How many times did you say you've been properly in love?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "You married two of them?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Well, I do mention in the book that the two marriages that I -- I ended up getting married to I was pregnant both times that I got married.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Or am I making an assumption there?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I have nothing going on in my life right now.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Have you matured fully or are you still slightly naughty?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Available, and available for a relationship, and not afraid of a relationship.", "docId": "120419pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "If I could find for you now the perfect man, based on all you've learned about love, romance, divorce, heartbreak, what would he be like?", "qSentId": 659}]